
export const data = [
  {
    question: "\\int_{2}^{3}xdx ",
    option1: "\\frac{5}{2}",
    option2: "\\frac{25}{x}",  
    option3: "\\sum_{i=1}^{n} \\alpha_i \\beta_i",
    option4: "\\frac{d}{dx} \\sin(x)",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{0}^{2} x^{3}dx",
    option1: "-\\frac{2^{x4}}{16}",
    option2: "\\frac{\\sqrt{x+2}}{2}",
    option3: "\\frac{d}{dx} \\cos(x)",
    option4: "4",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{0}^{4}3x^{2}dx",
    option1: "64",
    option2: "16",
    option3: "\\frac{x^{2}}{4}",
    option4: "\\sqrt{x^{3}}",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{5}^{2}4dt",
    option1: "\\frac{x^{5}}{2}",
    option2: "24",
    option3: "12",
    option4: "\\frac{x^{4}}{2^{2}}",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}cos^{3}t\\cdot sent dt",
    option1: "\\frac{x^{2x}}{senx}+C",
    option2: "\\frac{cosx^{2}}{x}+C",
    option3: "\\frac{cosx^{2}}{sen}+C",
    option4: "\\frac{senx^{3}}{3}+C",
    answer: 4,
  },
  //6
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}sen^{2}x\\cdot cosxdx",
    option1: "\\frac{sen^{3}x}{3}+C",
    option2: "\\frac{sen^{32}dx}{sen}+C",
    option3: "\\frac{cos^{2}x}{3}+C",
    option4: "\\frac{cosx^{2}}{sen}+C",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}\\frac{senx}{cos^{3}x}dx",
    option1: "\\frac{25}{x}",
    option2: "\\frac{1}{2cos^{2}x}+C",
    option3: "\\frac{costanx^{2}}{x}+C",
    option4: "\\frac{cos^{2}x}{3}+C",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}\\frac{cotx}{sen^{2}x}dx",
    option1: "\\frac{cos^{2}x}{3}+C",
    option2: "\\frac{1}{2cos^{4}x}+C",
    option3: "\\frac{-1}{2sen^{2}x}+C",
    option4: "\\frac{-2}{2sen^{2}x}+C",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}xe^{2x}dx",
    option1: "\\frac{x^{x}}{4}-\\frac{2}{8}e^{x}+C",
    option2: "\\frac{xe^{2x}}{2}+\\frac{1}{2}x^{4x}+C",
    option3: "\\frac{xe^{2x}}{2}-\\frac{1}{4}e^{2x}+C",
    option4: "\\frac{xe^{2x}}{2}+C",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}3xe^{x}dx",
    option1: "3xe^{x}-3e^{x}+C",
    option2: "e^{x}+3e^{2x}+C",
    option3: "e^{3x}+C",
    option4: "2xe^{4x}+5e^{5x}+C",
    answer: 1,
  },
  // 11
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}t^{2}e^{t}dt",
    option1: "e^{x}+3e^{2x}+C",
    option2: "te^{t}-e^{t}+C",
    option3: "2xe^{4x}+5e^{5x}+C",
    option4: "x^{t}-x^{et}+C",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}e^{x}senxdx",
    option1: "\\frac{-e^{x}cosx+e^{x}senx}{2}+C",
    option2: "\\frac{-e^{x}+C",
    option3: "\\frac{a^{2x}}{5}+C",
    option4: "\\frac{xe^{ab}}{5}+C",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}tan^{2}xdx",
    option1: "\\frac{x^{2}}{2}+C",
    option2: "senx-x^{cx}+C",
    option3: "xtanx-x^{2}+C",
    option4: "xtanx-x^{2}-ln|secx|-\\frac{x^{2}}{2}+C",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}z^{3}e^{z}dz",
    option1: "e^{z}+C",
    option2: "ze^{z}-e^{z}+C",
    option3: "ze^{z}-C2",
    option4: "zx^{z}+x^{2}+C",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}cos^{2}xsen^{3}xdx",
    option1: "\\frac{1}{5}cos^{5}x-\\frac{1}{3}cos^{3}x+C",
    option2: "\\frac{1}{3}cos^{3}x+C",
    option3: "\\frac{1}{5}cos^{3}x+C",
    option4: "\\frac{1}{5}sen^{3}x+C",
    answer: 1,
  },
// 16
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}cos^{8}xsen^{5}xdx",
    option1: "\\frac{2cos^{11}x}{11}-\\frac{sen^{15}x}{15}+C",
    option2: "\\frac{cos9x}{9}++C",
    option3: "\\frac{cos^{13}x}{13}+C",
    option4: "-\\frac{cos9x}{9}+\\frac{2cos^{11}x}{11}-\\frac{cos^{13}x}{13}+C",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}sec^{5}xtanxdx",
    option1: "\\frac{3}{11}cos^{4}x+C",
    option2: "\\frac{3}{11}cos^{5}x+C",
    option3: "\\frac{1}{5}sec^{5}x+C",
    option4: "cos^{x}x+C",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}tan^{6}xsec^{4}xdx",
    option1: "",
    option2: "\\frac{1}{7}tan^{7}x+\\frac{1}{9}tan^{9}x+C",
    option3: "",
    option4: "",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}sec^{3}xdx",
    option1: "",
    option2: "",
    option3: "\\frac{1}{2}\\left( secxtanx+ln|secx+tanx| \\right)+C",
    option4: "",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "\\int_{}^{}cos(5x)dx",
    option1: "",
    option2: "",
    option3: "",
    option4: "\\frac{1}{5}sen(5x)+C",
    answer: 4,
  },
];